SHUBHAM RAJ

Software Engineer

+917004922012

@ linkedin.com/in/shubhamraj9631/

@ shubhamraj43255@gmail.com

Gaya India



SUMMARY

Dedicated Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science student at Indian Institute of Information Technology Vadodara with a focus on honing skills in programming languages such as Python, C and Java. Proficient in the MERN stack, including HTML, MySQL, ReactJs, and JavaScript. Experienced in front end and full stack development through internships at OrSoot LLP and Solar Secure Solutions. Completed various training programs and online courses in web development. Strong project portfolio including Win99X, COVID Case Tracking, and Online Voting System. Committed to continuous learning and innovation in the tech industry.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

OrSoot LLP

= 01/2023 - 10/2023

Kanpur India

Work Responsibility

- To Create and maintained the user interface of the business website and gaming application.
- Make sure that the UI is compatible with a variety of hardware and software, including tablets, desktops, and mobile phones.
- To fulfil the requirements of the clients.

Full Stack Web Developer

Solar Secure Solutions

= 05/2022 - 07/2022

Ahmedabad India

Work Responsibility

- The objective of Online voting system is to help the organization in automating the whole manual processing of the existing system.
- The main objective to develop the system is to make the accurate & efficient decisions in different tasks at different time at different situations.
- System should support multi-user environment.
- System should provide concrete security features like creating users and assigning privileges to users of the system.
- System should be capable to keep track of all the detailed descriptions of the client and the whole details of services offered by the client organization.

EDUCATION

BS Software Engineering

Indian Institute of Information Technology Vadodara

Intermediate

Sanjay Singh Yadav College

SKILLS

HTML MySQL ReactJs

JavaScript

• PHP CSS

Microsoft Office

Data Structure

Node js

PROJECTS



- Win99X (2023)

Using HTML, CSS, Javascript, React. In Final Year intership projects



PORTFOLIO(2023)

- I created this project for my own resume. using HTML, CSS, Javascript



ONLINE VOTING SYSTEM(2022)

-Summer internship based projects. Using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP



HOSPITAL MANAGEMENT (2019)

-Create semester based projects. Using |C language.

CERTIFICATES

JavaScript (Basic) Certificate(Aug 2023)

Hackerrank

HTML, CSS, And JavaScriptfor web developers (Nov 20- Dec 20)

Coursera

The complete web development bootcamp(Jun 2022-Aug 2022)

Udemy

LANGUAGES

English Proficient

Hindi Native

